# **Isaac Oldwood**

8 Earning Street, Godmanchester, Huntingdon, Cambs, PE29 2JD 07955917768

Is a a c. Oldwood@gmail.com

D.O.B: 04/08/1998

## **Summary**

I am a very motivated individual with experience in customer facing jobs; I am more than willing to work flexible hours and I look forward to being a part of a unique team. I have great multitasking skills and I am able to work under pressure. I also develop software in my spare time; my language of choice is python, predominantly due to it being a scripting language. I have used various libraries such as numpy and pandas for data analysis. I use the requests library coupled with BeautifulSoup to write SeakerBots for Consortium and Ralph Lauren, amongst other projects. Also, I use pyautogui along with PIL to write bots for videogames. I am currently writing my own website with Flask which I host on my Raspberry Pi and learning penetration testing. I use GitHub to keep track of all my versions and commits, this shows I am proficient with Git. I feel as though I would be a good asset to your company.

#### Skills

Strong Verbal Communication	Confident	Punctual
Work Well in a Team	Competent in Python	Reliable
Fast Learner	Self-Motivated	Honest

## **Work History**

December 2018 to Current

## **Bar Staff**

I am employed by The Brickworks to work events held at their venue in Nottingham. My job involves taking orders, making drinks and taking payment. This shows aptitude in memory, dexterity and maths to remember the drinks, make the drinks and calculate the total and change-respectively. Most of the events are sold out which means the bar is very busy, this helps me gain confidence working under pressure and in a team. I also perform stock checks and restock the fridges if they are running low.

## September 2014 to Current

#### Maths Tutor

I have helped children from Year 6 through to Year 11 prepare for their Maths exams. I have been employed by the same families for over 4 years, which demonstrates that I am reliable, punctual and I can communicate well.

## November 2015 to December 2015

#### Santa Claus

My role as Santa Claus was a temporary job at Santa's Grotto at the Wyevale Centre. During my two months, my main role was working directly with customers, interacting with families with children of all ages. This further advanced my communication skills and taught me to deal with all kinds of

customers. My job was to talk to the children as Santa and ask them about their Christmas whilst trying to get the adults involved. I would then take a photo with them and give them a present. I sometimes had to deal with customers who were unhappy. This taught me to deal with situations, using good communication skills. Furthermore I maintained the grotto to ensure it was presentable, this included: sweeping, hoovering and organising the tables. I checked availability of stock and restocked the grotto when required; this included deciding on the appropriate presents to display.

#### June 2018

## **Bar Staff**

I was employed as bar staff at Detonate Festival- a one day festival in Nottingham. I was taught how the payment system worked which involved scanning the customer's wristband. I showed aptitude for the job as I was moved to the VIP bar after an hour. Due to it being a festival there was always a large crowd waiting to be served this taught me to work efficiently under pressure. Working behind the bar also developed my teamwork skills. At the VIP bar the customers had a choice of extra drinks, which included six cocktails. This means I had to learn how to make some basic cocktails, mix drinks and pull pints.

### Education

I am currently studying a Masters in Mathematics at the University of Nottingham and averaged a 2:1 across my first two years. I did my A-Levels at Hinchingbrooke Sixth Form and completed an A-level in Further Mathematics, Mathematics and Physics, obtaining BAB respectively. I also completed my GCSEs at Hinchingbrooke School Obtaining 2 A\*, 6 A, 4 B and a C including an A\* in Maths and a B in English.